Okechukwu Delight Ifeanyi

1,Sunday str off oremeji bus-stop, Alagbole-Akute, Lagos state

Contact: +2349163854228 Email: desolomon07@gmail.com

DOB: 30/07/2006

PROFILE

I am highly trusted freelance web and mobile developer, video animator, graphics and logo designer. I am consistent in my project over 30 projects to different clients. I have 4 years experience working in this areas and my experience on my training has shift me to become a good

expertise in my field and also added to my knowledge

SKILLS

- Web Development
- Graphics Design
- Python Programming
- Software Development
- Social Media
- Digital Marketing
- Affiliate Marketing
- Communication Skills
- Critical Thinking
- Time Management
- Decision Making
- Team Work
- Problem Solving
- · Personal Assistant

REFERENCE

Soenu Shakirullah - **Software Development** Lastveb

+2348022312904

INTERESTS

- Blockchain Technologies
- Exploring
- Participating in Social Activities
- Photoshop
- Gaming
- Dancing

EXPERIENCE

Delight Tech

Web and Graphics Design Duration: 2019 - Present

The Spark Foundation

Web and Mobile Development
Duration: June 2023 - August 2023

Emo fm - Radio Lagos

Maintenance

Duration: April 2022 - July 2022

EDUCATION

Government Technical College

Electronics Works

Passing Year - 2020-2023

Grades: Nabteb

Ojodu Junior Grammar School

Passing Year - 2017-2020

Grades: Bsce

PROJECTS

Technet Website & Job Board Website (2023-Present)

Maintaining the website entertaining, original and interactive while Applying the HTML, CSS, PHP and MYSQL skills and conducting different experiment.

School Website (2022-Present)

Creating the website with more of HTML, CSS and JavaScript and making it more interactive with some effects.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Certification:Ppl Academy (August 2023), Most willing to learn in the 2023 Technician Empowerment Program.